<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vee Dougherty</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vee Dougherty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:41:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vdougherty.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intersection of Mental Health and the Developer</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/intersection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:41:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/intersection/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://vdougherty.github.io/img/intersection.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          Recently, within the last few weeks, there was an attempted backdoor into Linux using XZ. You may have heard about it, you may have not. You can ...
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why this blog?</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/whythisblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:31:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/whythisblog/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          So, why a personal blog in this day and age of Facebook and a plethora of other micro-blogging sites? Certainly, there are more direct ways to...
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My lil&#39; Linux box - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/lillinuxboxpart2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:16:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/lillinuxboxpart2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://vdougherty.github.io/img/blog_lil_linux_desk.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          I still had some more research to do before I flashed my firmware. At this point, all I knew about the Chromebook was that it was small, lightweight and manufactured...
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My lil&#39; Linux box</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/lillinuxbox2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/lillinuxbox2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://vdougherty.github.io/img/lil_linux_laptop.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          Not too long ago I was offered a free Chromebook that a friend had no use for. I gladly accepted it, then placed it on shelf for a while, not really knowing what to do with it. I already had a... 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, Hello again</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/helloagain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:43:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/helloagain/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Apologies for the prolonged absence, but the blog is back and running after a year of basically being on the back burner. The unfortunate thing 	...
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That path thang</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/path/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://vdougherty.github.io/img/me_willamette_valley.jpeg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          So here we are recovering from our alcoholism, most of us in the first flush of sobriety are usually shocked at some point by the amount of wreckage...
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          I&amp;rsquo;ve had the good fortune to work either directly or via contract for:
DDB Needham
Black Dot Group
WebStreet Securities
Allstate
PartnerData
Pampered Chef
Office Max/Office Depot
FTD
Sears
I choose to focus on PartnerData in this instance as example of what I can do with out making this page overly long. It should suffice as an illustration of my talents, think of it as a jumping off point to pursue further conversations of how I can help your organization.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sound</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/sound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/sound/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Bands #  I’ve been a professional musician since the late 80’s. Below is a brief sampling of music that I wrote either solo or in bands situations. I’ve enjoyed some notoriety, but also have learned that it takes roughly 6 months for your artistry to make it to the cut out bin… oof-da. Along the way I’ve made countless life-long friendships with some of the coolest people you would ever want to meet.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/vision/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Portfolio #  Welcome to a brief portfolio page. I have worked in various settings from advertising, promotional to corporate communications. From start ups to Fortune 500 companies. I’ve lead teams of developers and designers. I’ve also been just a team member. The selections below demonstrate what I call working “small to large” or integrated promotional marketing. Small - being website graphics, large - being anything larger then standard print sizes.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 13:26:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://vdougherty.github.io/img/me_willamette_valley.jpeg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          Welcome to my personal blog. Complete with a small portfolio of this and that. So, use the navigation at the top right and explore away...
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Well, hello there&amp;hellip; #  I live in the PNW, as a recent transplant from the city of Chicago. I&amp;rsquo;m an artist, a musician, a generalist in all geek/nerd sub-culture, and a daily user of Linux. I&amp;rsquo;m a trained Illustrator (multiple years of drawing naked people in art school, to get my degree) who fell into Web Design/Development. I was lucky, when after my first-semester of Web Design, a major ad agency selected me to work in their bustling Chicago-office.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://vdougherty.github.io/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vdougherty.github.io/archive/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>